One deadly tournament. Last fight for freedom.
Undisputed III: Redemption is a action, thriller,
crime film directed by Isaac Florentine.
Russian inmate Boyka, now severely hobbled by the knee
injury suffered at the end of Undisputed 2.
No longer the feared prison fighter he was, he has declined so
far that he is now good only for cleaning toilets.
But when a new prison fight tournament begins - an international affair, matching the best fighters from prisons around the globe, enticing
them with the promise of freedom for the winner - Boyka must reclaim his dignity and fight for his position in the tournament.
Yuri Boyka, played by Scott Adkins.
Turbo, played by Mykel Shannon Jenkins.
Gaga, played by Mark Ivanir.
Warden Kuss, played by Hristo Shopov.
Raul 'Dolor' Quinones, played by Marko Zaror.
Casino Manager, played by Michael Baral.
Undisputed III: Redemption is a 2010 American martial arts action film directed by Isaac Florentine
and starring Scott Adkins, Mykel Shannon Jenkins, Mark Ivanir and Hristo Shopov.
It is the sequel to Undisputed II: Last Man Standing (2007), and the
third installment overall in the Undisputed franchise.
The film explores themes of prison, showdown, fight, shotgun, prison cell.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.